<topics>
  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-cherry-blossom-trees</id>
    <results>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85042462/1909-10-19/ed-1/?sp=3&q=Mikado+Cherry+Trees</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          MANY CHERRY TREES
          SHIPPED BY MIKADO
          JAPAN SENDS U. S. OVER 2000
          FINE SPECIMENS
          Many Saplings from Orient Will B«
          Planted Along Potomac and Riv
          erside Driveways Mrs.
          Taft Recipient
          WASHINGTON, Oct. 18.—When tha
          honorary commercial commissioners of
          Japan arrives in Washington, Novem
          ber 1, they will be taken on an auto
          mobile ride which will include Poto
          mac drive, along which 2000 cherry
          trees to be presented to this country
          by the emperor of Japan are to be
          planted.
          The shipment of the trees and the
          planting thereof have been entrusted
          to Toraklro Watase, proprietor of a
          Tokio plant and seed company, who
          is one of the commissioners.
          Speaking of the gift of the emperor
          to the city of Washington, Mr. Watase
          said the trees would be sent to Mrs.
          Taft, wife of the president, and by
          her presented to the government for
          transplanting- along- Potomac drive.
          Former President Roosevelt and
          President Taft are chiefly responsible
          for the improvement of the Potomac
          river front, and it was Mrs. Taft ivho
          gave the name Potomac park to that
          section of the city. She made popular
          the afternoon promenades on the drive,
          which were a feature last year of
          summer life in the capital.
          New York Remembered
          The emperor of Japan Is sending to
          New York also a large number of
          cherry trees to be planted along River
          side drive and Grant's tomb.
          In Japan, the land of the cherry
          blossom, there are many beautiful
          legends about the trees and flower of
          the cherry.
          The blossom of the Japanese cherry
          is of a peculiarly delicate beauty, and
          there is a tradition in Japan that if
          that same tone appears in the blos
          soms of the Japanese cherry planted
          in another country, that country can
          he taken and subjugated by Japan.
          Mr. Watase is authority for the
          statement that while many Japanese
          cherry trees have been brought to the
          United States, the color of the bloa
          eoms, although just as beautiful, is
          unlike the blossom which appears in
          Japan.
          •Therefore," he said, "we conclude
          that we could not take America, even
          if we were so disposed."
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86069675/1910-01-19/ed-1/?sp=5&q=Cherry+Trees</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          japanese Cherry Trees Present
          ed Mrs Taft
          The Emperor of Japans re
          membrance of President Taft s
          great enjoyment of the cherry
          blossom festival season when in i
          Japan has taken the graceful form
          of the presentation to Mrs Taft
          of three car loads of young cherry
          trees and they are now in Wash
          ington
          The greatest care bas been tekeen
          all the way from the land of the
          Mikado to keep the iemperature
          an uneven stage that the trees
          Tuftns i
          in apprpciutiou tile oppuntunity
          for a cherry blossom 
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1910-01-29/ed-1/?sp=6&q=Mikado+Cherry+Trees</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
        <text>
          MAYOR OF TOKYO HERE TO SEE AND STUDY CITY
          The mayor of Tokyo is a guest of Washington, and before he goes back he’ll know a great deal about municipalities in the United States and the commission form of government as illustrated in the Capital. He came here to study and see the sights. With his wife he is registered at the Shoreham as “Y. Oyake and Madame, of Tokyo, Japan.”
          The mayor is a handsome little Nippon of forty years, and his wife is about ten years younger than he. They are attired in American clothes for the most part, but there is an Oriental aspect that makes it easy to distinguish them as Japanese from the metropolis of the far-away island.
          Japanese of the Capital will give a welcome to the distinguished visitor today, but no programme has been given out. It is probable a reception will be given at the Japanese legation.
          Mayor Oyake is a friend of President Taft, and the State Department announced yesterday that he would pay a visit to the President while here. When President Taft went to Japan several years ago as Secretary of War he was entertained by the mayor of Tokyo.
          Mayor Oyake was once exiled from Japan on account of his political activities, but he came back and built up his power again. He was a member of the Mikado’s privy council, and held many distinguishing offices.
          As a mark of friendship, Mayor Oyake sent 1,000 cherry trees to Mrs. Taft recently, but the cherry trees became infected and did not live.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1910-01-29/ed-1/?sp=6&q=Mikado+Cherry+Trees&st=text&r=0.437,0.75,0.571,0.571,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          TO DESTROY JAPANESE TREES.
          Gifts from Tokio to Wasnington Found
          To Be Badly Diseased.
          Washington, Jan. 2S.— Regret has been
          expressed by the President and by Mrs.
          Taft because two thousand Japanese
          cherry trees presented by the municipality
          of Toklo to this government for use In the
          national capita' have been found to be
          Ir.fected with root gall worms, certain dis
          eases and Insect pests, some of the latter
          hitherto unknown in this country. The
          trees were to have been planted in Poto
          m;\c Park, wl^.ich Mrs. Taft did much last
          year to have made the outdoor boulevard
          and meeting place of social ashington.
          The Secretar of Agriculture s.,- .m
          It necessary to recommend the destruc
          tion of the trees. Secretary Knox lias ex
          ptm i to the Japanese Ambassador the
          regret of the government authorities that
          the gift cannot be used, and Colonel Cosby,
          in charge of Public Building" and Grounds,
          has conveyed reyrets to the Mayor of
          Toklo.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016187/1910-12-22/ed-1/?sp=5&q=Cherry+Trees</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          It will be remembered that tho Em
          peror of Japan last Spring sent several
          thousand Japanese cherry trees to Mrs
          Taft to be placed along the Iotomac
          Drive which she originated These
          cherry trees were found to be infected
          witha peculiar injurious Japanese in
          sect and for fear they would contami
          nate the cherry trees In this country
          the whole lot was burned It is now
          announced that the Japanese authori
          ties are sending another consignment
          of cherrj trees that have been exam
          ined and shown to be clear of all dis
          ease Mrs Taft has on numerous occa
          sions been honored by the Japanese
          Government In the White House thero
          is a magnificent and well nigh priceless
          cabinet of Japanese lacquer inlaid with
          gold which was presented to Mrs Taft
          by the Empress of Japan when she
          was abroad with President Taft In
          the cabinet are also two unique vases
          in silver containing bouquets of silver
          flowers She was also presented with
          a number of Japanese dolls that are
          cutely attractive and also very valua
          ble
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026749/1913-04-06/ed-1/?sp=10&q=Cherry+Trees&r=0.394,0.128,0.85,0.482,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          In all the riot of blossoms which have burgeoned forth in Potomac Park within the last week to make that stretch the most gorgeous anywhere in the District, there is none which shows more delicate beauty than the blossoms on the Japanese cherry trees which were presented to the United States by the government of Japan a year ago. These fragrant, beautiful trees are blooming now for the first time. The river drive, from the Virginia bridge up to Twenty-third street, is fragrant with them, and thousands have stopped their carriages to admire the delicate beauty of the bloom.
          Unlike the domestic cherry, the Japanese variety leans more to bloom than it does to fruit. The chief trouble in the care seems to be spent in pruning the wonderfully long branches which droop and cover the limbs. The trees are trimmed every year, but the task takes a year and of course hope is entertained that it will be more like reclamation. The pruning knife has no opportunity to work toward symmetry and the branches spread awkwardly above and below.
          Blossoms Are Beautiful
          The blossoms, however, are as beautiful now as they will be in years to come and make the observer forget the shape of the tree. In appearance, the blooms are a delicate pink shading almost to white in some instances, with a cluster in nature more like the individual blossoms which are found on plants like the wild rose.
          A little over a year ago the Department of Agriculture received a consignment of several hundred cherry trees from Japan. One of the shipments of trees was found to be infected with a strange disease, and, for fear that the entire consignment might be threatened, experts at the head of the department considered destroying the consignment of several hundred trees. Closer inspection disclosed that the trees were in the minority, but, rather than use the infected ones, the remainder were planted.
          The original intention was to plant the cherry trees all over the District of Columbia, but after the disease was discovered the plan was changed and the trees planted along the reclaimed section of the Potomac. In this location, they would be safely removed from infection, and, if necessary, destroy further. It was deemed unwise to disseminate the plant life over a wider area until it stamped out.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84026749/1919-04-07/ed-1/?sp=3&q=Cherry+Trees&r=0.503%2C0.069%2C0.817%2C0.463%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Japan has come to the United
          States Just a little bit of the Flowery
          Kingdom, to be sure tmt enough to
          make even the most unimaginative
          person long to see "cherry felosjoa
          time In Nippon.
          Down at the Tidal Basin, the other
          side of the Monument, a galaxy of
          Japanese cherry trees are Is full and
          fragrant bloom blooms that are try
          Ing to say with U. their delicate
          pinkness and sweetness that -spring
          Is here, that they live "but to weave
          garlands for her costumes and
          wreath lor her hair.
          Yesterday every member of the
          Japanese embassy made a pilgrimage
          to the- cherry trees from their own
          far-away country stood In wonder
          and delight at the sight of the flowers
          they love so well. It was like being
          transported "back to Japan for a few
          happy moments, they said.
          But it's only a sample of what
          Japan really looks like, they declare,
          for In their country the trees are tea
          times as big as our trees, although
          not a whit lovelier, for the climate
          here Is ideal for the full flowering of
          the- Japanese trees.
          Th cherry trees' came tc as
          straight from Japan several years
          ago and begged a home in this jeeaa
          try. What could be, more appro
          priate for a dwelling' place than the
          National Capital and what more, de
          lightful and easily accessible location
          than that around the Tidal Basin
          So they- were planted and took new
          coot and life and every sprfng 'will
          display more profuse and lovelier
          charms
          It was the city of Tokyo, throcxh
          the mayor, which made It possible. fpr
          Washingtonlans to have a glimpse of
          Japan as it looks in the unforgettable
          springtime, which has1 always' been
          the Inspiration of poets arid loyers.
          Thousands of miles away' little
          Japanese maidens plight their troth
          under the cherry trees, and Just to
          demonstrate that maidens of every
          time and clime are not very much, un
          like, alm&st any bright, sunshiny day
          can find little American maidens
          walking- hand and nand with very
          American boys under the- rtrr same
          kind of trees, saying the very same
          kind of things that the cherry blos
          soms have heard for centuries is
          their own country.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045433/1912-03-28/ed-1/?sp=12&q=Cherry+Trees&st=text&r=0.066,0.628,0.558,0.558,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
        <text>
          JAPANESE TREES IS TOPIC.
          Miss E. It. Scldntore o Address
          tlounl Geographic Society.
          Descriptions of a variety of Japanese
          trees, which have Just been received In
          Washington and are to be planted In Po
          tomac Park, will be given by Mies E. R.
          Scldmore. who Is to address the National
          Geographic Society to morrow at 4 15
          o clock and again at 8 IS o'clock at New
          Masonic Temple.
          Her subject will be "Japanese gar
          dens," an exposition of the theories and
          rules of Japanese landscape gardening
          The lecture will be illustrated wltholor-
          ed lantern slides, and Miss Scldmore will
          show pictures of .fifty different varieties'
          Japanese cherry blossoms Miss
          Scldmore. who Is the author of "Jlnrlk
          Isha Da j s In Japan." Is an authority on
          Japanese life and habits, and It la ex
          pected that memDers or tne Japanese
          Embassy, as well as many members of
          the diplomatic corps, will attend tne
          lecture.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045462/1921-03-27/ed-1/?sp=61&q=Cherry+Blossom+tree+japan+tidal+Basin&r=-0.254,0.687,0.697,0.395,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          No other flower in all the world is so beloved and worshiped as sakura-no-hana, the cherry blossom of Japan. It is Nihon-ga-hana, "the flower of Japan," and if one says "flower" without specifying, cherry blossom is always understood. It is the national flower, the symbol of purity, the emblem of chivalry and knightly honor, the crest of a cult whose main celebration has endured these two thousand years. It is Japan's own and dearer to her than any other verdure. The world-famous cherry blossoms of old Japan are as old as the nation itself. Nara-Yamato rulers brought branches of them in the fifth century from their hunting parties in the back mountains and planted them in the palace grounds.
          In the fifth century the emperor and his court used to go to the "Palace of a Thousand Cherry Trees," near Nara, to view the blossoms and make boating excursions on the cherry-bordered lake. The court and the custom continues to the present day, and all the empire is given over to holiday pleasures while the sakuras are on.
          Millions of poems have been written to the cherry blossoms and the branches of blossoming trees, and in this age of steam and electricity the cult continues. Hideyoshi, the Taiko, man of blood and iron of those days, the "Napoleon of Japan," held a cherry blossom and poetry party of 5,000 guests in the golden palace on the mountain slope, and again had as many at another cherry blossom festival at Yoshino, in Yamato, the very home of cherry blossoms. In these days when the glass age has covered all the hills and ravines and masses of the "ten thousand trees" at Yoshino, the cherry blossom age reigns supreme. And so it endures as many another famous view.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82016187/1909-12-23/ed-1/?sp=5&q=Cherry+Trees+Mikado&r=0.087,0.69,0.331,0.188,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Our new Potomac Park down beyond
          the monument is to be beautified by
          Japanese cherry trees Col Cosby Su
          perintendent of Public Buildings and
          Grounds has been informed by Jukio
          OzakI the Mayor of Tokyo Japan that
          the 2000 cherry trees which were pre
          sented to the city of Washington have
          arrived at Seattle and will be shipped
          at once to this city Tho Mayor of
          Tokyo said in his letter It gives me
          great pleasure to inform you that the
          corporation of Tokyo at a recent meet
          ing of its Councils resolved to present
          2000 Japanese cherry trees to the Gov
          ernment of the United States for tho
          use of the city of Washington And
          the Mayor goes on to say The cherry
          trees are extensively cultivated in this
          country and are the most admired of
          the flowering trees Ten of the most
          representative kinds have been selected
          and I beg to assure you that it will re
          main to the citizens of Tokyo a pleas
          ing memory as well as a matter of civic
          pride to know that their small offering
          will be permitted to contribute to the
          advancement of the beautiful Capital
          of the great Republic which they all
          admire
        </text>
      </result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84036228/1905-09-19/ed-1/?sp=5&q=cherry+blossom&r=-0.198,0.088,0.967,0.633,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          "Should you ask me what Is the
          true spirit of Japan I would answer—
          'tis the scent of the mountain cherry
          tree in the morning air," says the
          poet Motoori, beloved of the Japan
          ese.
          The scent of the mountain cherry
          trtee in the morning air! 'Tis a peace
          odor that, which wins the hearts of
          aliens even, and when I think how it
          must permeate the happy memories
          of each of the little brown sons and
          daughters of this tinkling, small,
          sweet land of elfln faiths, writes Ele
          anor Franklin. I believe I understand
          the "true spirit of Japan," that Yama
          to damashi which is at once the re
          ligion and the pride earth earthy of the
          country of mysteries screened by fan
          tasy.
          The cherry blossom is the emblem
          of Bushido; Bushido is Japanese chiv
          alry; the soul of Japan so enthusias
          tically dwelt upon by that best inter
          preter for his own, Inazo Nitobe, A.
          M„ Ph. D. The cherry blossom, be
          loved for itself and not, as by us,
          for what it promises, is native to Ja
          pan, as native as the firmly fixed be
          lief in Ama-terasu, the Heaven-Shin
          ing-Great-August Deity, Goddess of
          the Sun, whose descendant, now aug
          ustly deigning to sit upon the throne
          of the empire, is the first of this great
          line who has ever been fearlessly look
          ed upon by his adoring subjects.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86075250/1954-06-25/ed-1/?sp=4&q=cherry+blossom&r=-0.119%2C0.087%2C0.686%2C0.449%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          In the next half century Japan
          1 amazed the world with her swift
          adoption of modern mechanization
          and methods.
          In 1912, capital of several thous
          and cherry trees. The presentat-
          I ion was a symbol of the old Japan
          iof flower festivals and stylized
          i scenic effects.
          I Prior to 1912 there were few Jap
          anese cherry trees in the United
          States.though it was known that
          they would thrive here.
          Dr. David Fairchild, the world
          renowned plant explorer who now
          Uvea In coconut Grove, Flordia, had
          imported several varieties in the
          early 1900’s and had successfully
          grown them in his garden outside
          Washington.
          From trees planted by Dr. Fair
          child came the idea for the miles
          of plantings in the capital’s Potom
          ac Park. His flowering oriental
          j cherries were seen and admired by
          Miss Eliza Scidmore. a writer long
          j interested in Japan’s histroy and
          culture.
          1 Through her efforts, the mayor
          !of Toyko arranged to have some
          3.000 shoots from Toyko’s famous
          riverside front sent to Washington
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86075229/1958-04-03/ed-1/?sp=9&q=cherry+blossom&st=text&r=0.13,0.592,0.52,0.52,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Cherry Blossom Time. The
          Cherry trees in Washington haven't
          had the advantage of nice weather
          like Montana has had these past
          several weeks, and consequently, did
          not bloom in time for the annual
          Cherry Blossom Festival.
          The festivities went forward any
          way, with sunshine arriving in the
          Capital a day after the program be
          gan. 
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84027524/1953-05-15/ed-1/?sp=5&q=cherry+blossom&st=text&r=0,0.259,0.396,0.396,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
        <text>
          Royalty of Flathead's East Shore are these members of cherry
          blossom court crowned Sunday at Yellow Bay Community club
          house. Cherry blossom queen for 1953 is Mary Jane Kurth, Big
          fork high school senior. Her princesses are Gail Powell and Sue
          Mechler with Polly Peppard, 6, the crown bearer. Nat Boyd, sales
          manager of Flathead Lake Cherry Growers' Association crowned the
          queen. Group then proceeded to Upper Bear Dance clubhouse. Here
          as at the Yellow Bay center, cherry pie, ice cream, cake and coffee
          were served. About 1,500 automobiles drove the East Shore road
          to view cherry blossoms and festiv ities.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88064055/1920-06-17/ed-1/?sp=3&q=cherry+blossom&st=text&r=0.45,0.468,0.547,0.547,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
        <text>
          CHERRY FLAVORED DRINK
          The new soft drink, "CHERRY
          BLOSSOM," has the real taste. Try
          a bottle of it at dealers in soft
          drinks.
        </text>
      </add_result>
    </results>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-czar-nicholas-ii</id>
    <results>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn92070477/1894-11-07/ed-1/?sp=8&q=Alexander+Czar+Nicholas&r=0.104,0.133,1.013,0.574,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Last Thursday afternoon at 2:15 the
          czar of Russia passed peacefully away.
          His death had been expected for several
          days. Early in the morning the czar
          expressed a desire to see the czarewitch
          and conversed with him in private for
          several minutes. The czarewitch replied
          in a few words and bent down and kissed
          his father's lips. Then the emperor
          asked all of his children to come to his
          side. In a weak but perfectly audible
          voice the dying man addressed his chil
          dren. Then taking the hand of the em
          press he, for the first time during his
          illness, showed sighs of deep emotion.
          After this the czar seemed to Ihj some
          what more cheerful and frequently ad
          dressed words of comfort to the empress.
          Toward 2 o'clock his breathing became
          more labored and a violent fit of cough
          ing brought on a slight hemorrhage, fol
          lowed by faintness. When this had par
          tially passed away, the czar turned to
          speak once more to his family, but the
          empress, who was supporting him.could
          not hear his words, and almost immedi
          ately afterwards ho sighed deeply and
          ceased to breathe. His end was most
          peaceful.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84036012/1896-05-24/ed-1/?sp=14&q=Czar+Nicholas&r=0.276,1.003,0.726,0.411,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
           Dr. Talmage and I were waited on, one delightful day in July, 1892, by Count Bobrinskoy, a warm personal friend of the present czar, and a military attache of the emperor. We were driven down the Nevsky Prospect—the Broadway of St. Petersburg—to the railway station, where a special train was in readiness to take us to Peterhof, the summer residence of the imperial family.
          We had received instructions as to dress—full dress suit, white tie and white gloves, the right hand ungloved—and thus attired and full of delightful anticipations, we were whirled along through a charming country—Count Bobrinskoy meanwhile making innumerable inquiries in regard to such American affairs as specially enlisted his interest.
          "You will find the caesarevitch of quite a retiring disposition," said he, changing the subject, "and should there be a lull in the conversation, please do not construe it as a hint that the audience is ended. The caesarevitch is greatly interested in your country and its institutions, and you will find him a good listener; but he mistrusts his knowledge of English grammar, and is therefore deliberate when using that language."
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>1</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Since the day he ascended the throne
          there has been a continuous contest
          between his wife ar.d his mother for
          supremacy over the Czar. His mother,
          the Dowager Empress, though brought
          up at the most democratic court in
          Europe that of Denmark— became
          after her marriage to Alexander III as
          Muscovite in thought and opinion as
          the most extreme Russian Conserv
          atives. A Protestant by birth and edu
          cation, she became a devout adherent
          of the orthodox Greek faith.
          When her son. Nicholas II, then a
          young man of "6, became Emperor, his
          mother formed a resolve that she would
          guide him in the footsteps of his
          fathers and protect him from the mod
          ernizing influences of the age. The
          Dowager Empress has been the lead
          ing spirit of the reactionists at the
          Russian court. She has sought to make
          her eon a ruler after her own heart, a
          statesman of the Muscovite school, a
          The truth is that the Czar Nicholas II
          is physically weak, with shattered
          nerves, and without much will of his
          own. He is an amiable young man and
          well-meaning: enough, but he is abso
          lutely unfitted to be the autocratic
          ruler of a country like Russia, where
          an iron-handed administrator is essen
          tial.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn82015679/1904-02-07/ed-1/?sp=35&q=Czar+little+nicholas</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          HOW THE CZAR RULES
          AND HOW
          HE IS RULED
          It is a much-debated question, even in the best in
          formed Russian circles, how far the Czar rules an 1
          how far he is ruled by his ministers Nicholas has
          fchown himself to be humane, conscientious, and
          sincerely desirous to promote his people's welfare
          and preserve the peace of the world. At his own re
          quest, during the famine of 1891. he was made
          president of the Committee of Succor by his father,
          and he worked very hard in the organization of re
          lief. His work in the cause of peace is well known
          to the world. It is a curious fact that, although
          he received a military education and has held several
          military commands, he has always entertained the
          strongest dislike of militarism.
          But Nicholas jv emphatically an autocrat. He has
          always insisted CM being an absolute ruler, dis
          missing several ministers for acting without his au
          thority and rejecting all suggestions to give a Con
          stitution to Russia. Unfortunately, it is easier for
          an autocrat to make war than to keep the peace
          A Russian Czar can make war by a word, but he
          might not be able to resist a deluge of facts, figure-,
          documents and arguments in favor of war. Hi
          ministers can render his autocratic power useless, as
          they have done over and over again, by presenting
          a case in such a manner as to make only one de
          cision possible.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90059523/1905-01-24/ed-1/?sp=1&q=Czar+Yacht&r=-0.054%2C0.923%2C0.615%2C0.403%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          ST. PETERSBURG, Jan. 23.—The Russian revolution has
          begun. The bloody dawn of the day of freedom will be fol
          lowed by more slaughter, but in the end the people will tri
          umph. Sunday's 'awful proceedings have accomplished
          what years of propaganda could not accomplish. Confidence
          in the czar—the strongest article in the faith of the common
          people of Russia —has been destroyed. This has been the in
          surmountable breastwork behind which the aristocrats have
          fought off every movement for reform in Russia. They have
          shielded themselves behind the traditional love of the people
          lor their supreme ruler.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030272/1905-11-01/ed-1/?sp=8&q=Czar+Concessions+Nicholas+Russia&st=image&r=-0.129,0.4,0.776,0.508,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The Czar’s Concessions.
          To ascertain the precise purport of the concessions made by NICHOLAS II to his people’s demand for representative institutions we should disregard headlines and all unofficial interpretations and fix our eyes on the exact words of the imperial manifesto and of the only trustworthy commentary—namely, Count WITTE’S report, on which the Czar with his own hands inscribed the words “To be taken for guide.” As we have both of these documents, we can construe them for ourselves.
          Let us begin by noticing what we do not find in the manifesto. The Czar does not grant to his subjects what in English speaking countries we are accustomed to regard as the palladium of individual liberty: that is to say, he does not authorize the courts to issue a writ of habeas corpus. That is the one efficient method of assuring in practice the “inviolability of person” which the Czar vaguely promises and orders his Government to assure.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85066387/1911-10-01/ed-1/?sp=5&q=Czar+home+Nicholas</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The Czar has read Dostoyevsky, Turgenieff and Gogol; but in German translations. The English and French authors whose works I remember having seen at the table of the Russian Imperial family were: Oscar Wilde, George Meredith, Mark Twain, Balzac, Maupassant and Anatole France.
          After luncheon the Czar would rest for an hour, play cards or chess with the chamberlain or the court dames, or entertain the children. From four o’clock until five, he would receive his Cabinet Ministers and other officials. At six o’clock dinner was served. After dinner, the Czar would visit the Czarina, sit on a rocking chair before the fireplace and listen to stories, told or read by some court lady or a guest invited specially for that purpose. Twice during the week, artists from the Imperial Opera were commanded to attend at the Palace and to render vocal and instrumental selections.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030272/1912-07-07/ed-1/?sp=48&q=Czar+Nicholas&r=0.387,0.973,0.527,0.345,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          "God is high up in the skies and the Czar is far away," says the Russian peasant as he humbly lies down under the knout or he gives a bribe to some functionary.
          The intelligent classes in Russia were displeased with the conduct of the Czarevitch, foreseeing a new, insignificant reign. In the court spheres all kinds of wild and impossible stories were circulating while the royal travellers were returning home.
          The journey brought nothing new into the life of Nicholas, and upon his return he became again absorbed in the life of his regiment. Only from time to time he attended his lectures or the meetings of the council concerning the construction of the Siberian railroad.
          The routine made itself felt everywhere. Alexander was not fond of military service, yet he did not make any attempt to influence his son in that direction. Having directed his own attention and all his efforts to suppressing revolutionary activities in the Russian land and oppressing the people at the same time, he neglected the education of the successor to the Russian throne. Nicholas knew practically nothing about the internal affairs of his country, and when he became Czar all who needed it made use of his ignorance.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1917-03-18/ed-1/?dl=page&q=czar+dethroned+nicholas&sp=11&st=image&r=0.045,0.14,0.917,0.6,0</id>
        <rel>0</rel>
        <text>
          This modern miracle of the pianoforte—the Ampico—brings you the music you love in your home. All the playing of the great concert pianists of the day will be reproduced exactly for you. Tone for tone, tempo for tempo, each minute cadence will come to you with the glowing magnetism of the gifted artist.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88084272/1918-07-30/ed-1/?sp=4&q=Czar+Nicholas+death+die&r=-0.157,0.072,0.516,0.338,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          NICHOLAS ROMANOFF, former czar of Russia and head of the church, ruler of half of Europe and much of Asia, is dead officially. The Russian wireless (official) out of Moscow announces his execution. His actual death probably occurred some time before the Bolshevik government saw fit to announce it officially. The official announcement, however, may be regarded as complete confirmation of the fact that none could be so interested in establishing the authenticity of the former czar's demise than the Lenines and Trotskys whose tenure of authority the existence of Nicholas continually menaced.
          Things in Russia are mixed up most curiously. Lenine and Trotsky have been charged with being in German pay; with having, at German direction, engineered events leading up to the signature of the infamous Brest-Litovsk peace treaty by which Germany was given outright a large part of Russia and a mortgage on the rest. Maybe so. Indications lend color of truth to that assertion.
          But Lenine and Trotsky hated the czar and probably sought means of getting him under the sod. They succeeded, apparently. If the Russian official statement is correct, Nicholas was shot dead, without trial, without a chance to defend himself, and his soul has gone to join the shades of other tyrants.
        </text>
      </result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn87065632/1917-03-23/ed-1/?sp=4&q=czar+nicholas+ii&r=-0.108%2C0.397%2C0.898%2C0.588%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The abdication of Emperor
          Nicholas II means that "the peo
          ple have finally revolted against
          the tyrany of their rulers and
          are determined to exercise their
          rights in establishing a constitu
          tional government. The deposed
          czar, Nicholas II, succeeded to
          the throne in 1894. Under the
          influence of his cabinet his gov
          ernment grew oppressive and
          finally in 1906 a revdlution
          brought about the formation of
          the Duma, the legislative body
          of the Russian government.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83016025/1894-11-02/ed-1/?sp=1&q=czar+nicholas+ii&r=0.167%2C0.483%2C0.454%2C0.297%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          ‘It is understood that Czar Nicholas II., will
          be proclaimed tomorrow, and that the
          Grand Duke George Alexander 111., the
          second son, no'v ill in Caucaucus, will be
          declared heir, and that the troops and state
          officials will take the oath of loyalty and
          allegiance on Saturday.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn87062015/1917-03-17/ed-1/?sp=1&q=czar+nicholas+ii&r=0.011%2C0.411%2C0.539%2C0.353%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Abdication of
          Czar Nicholas II., failed to save the Romanoff dynasty j
          ami government by the reigning family is at an end. j
          Russia is now governed by the "committee of twelve,
          headed bv Rodziankis, and will be under its control until j
          the meeting of a constitutional assembly.
          Czar Nicholas signed .the formal abdication of the,
          Romanoffs from the throne on behalf of himself and the^
          heir apparent on Thursday.
          Grand Duke Michael, oldest brother of the czar, who
          was indicated as regent when the czar attempted to ab
          dicate in favor of his son, himself abdicated yesterday,
          thus bringing the Romanoff dynasty to an end. 
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86063790/1917-03-29/ed-1/?sp=6&q=czar+nicholas+ii&st=text&r=-0.225,-0.026,0.799,0.799,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The character of Czar Nicholas II,
          of Russia, has been a theme of many
          contradictions. On one point, however.
          all chronicles have agreed, and
          that has been in regard to the essential
          timidity of the man.
          Circumstantial stories have been
          circulated from country to country
          during the progress of the great war
          that the czar was secretly maintaining
          a confidential correspondence
          with the kaiser.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn96060002/1917-03-19/ed-1/?sp=5&q=czar+nicholas+ii&st=image&r=-0.056,0.052,0.6,0.393,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          LONDON, Mar. 15.—As the result of the revolution which has been brewing for some time, Czar Nicholas II of Russia today abdicated his throne, and Grand Duke Michael Alexandrovitch, Nicholas’ younger brother, automatically becomes regent of the empire till Nicholas’ small son is old enough to assume the duties of emperor. It is unknown here whether or not the revolutionists will allow the reins of government to remain in the hands of the royal family.
          The news of the revolution came as a bolt out of the blue, as the public had no intimation of any serious internal disorders in Russia. The censors have been withholding all news on this subject from the newspapers since the outbreak of actual hostilities a week ago.
        </text>
      </add_result>
    </results>
  </topic>

  <topic>
    <id>https://guides.loc.gov/chronicling-america-john-rockefeller</id>
    <results>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86091092/1891-06-27/ed-1/?sp=2&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Although John D. Rockefeller thus seems to be the richest man in America he lives in a comparatively modest fashion. He has never built a palace on Fifth avenue, and his equipage is not of that gorgeous character calculated to attract attention on the street. His New York house is at No. 4 West Fifty-fourth street, opposite St. Luke's Hospital. The house is surrounded by spacious grounds and is handsomely furnished, but there is no ostentatious or even notable display of the evidences of wealth. There are no servants in livery; in fact, there are no men-servants whatever. The door is opened by a maid in cap and apron, and maid-servants wait on the table. It has been repeatedly remarked, by the way, that Mr. Rockefeller looks like a preacher.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn90059523/1896-08-02/ed-1/?sp=13&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil&r=0.062%2C1.14%2C0.345%2C0.226%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          It was in 1857 when John D. Rockefel
          ler, then a young man of nineteen,
          met M. B. Clark, who is now a member
          of the elevator firm of Gardner, Clark
          York.
          The two young men rented a store
          and went into the commission business
          on their own account. They succeeded
          in a moderate way. Rockefeller con
          tinued to save his share of the prof-
          Its as he had saved his salary, and in
          the eight years during which the part
          nership continued he had put aside
          something like $5,000.
          Then the young man was again
          stricken with a feeling of restlessness.
          He was not making money fast
          enough. The commission business had
          apparently reached Its limit He
          looked about him for an investment
          in something more profitable. Dis
          satisfaction is sometimes mere ambi
          tion after all.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83040052/1902-04-25/ed-1/?sp=1&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil&r=-0.025%2C0.673%2C0.973%2C0.637%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Mr. John D. Rockefeller reminds the world
          of his existence at this moment by giving
          5250,000 to Barnard College for Women and
          by compelling or inducing others to give 250,
          000 more.
          It must be said for Mr. Rockefeller that what
          he takes away through an ingenious display of
          force and skill combined, he occasionally gives
          back to the people very intelligently.
          Mr. Rockefeller has given many millions to
          the cause of education.
          Whatever you may think of his way of get
          ting the millions, you cannot deny him grati
          tude for the motive and intelligence which
          direct his gifts.
          Mr. Rockefeller's money "does much for edu
          cation. Mr. Rockefeller himself is a great
          national educator.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn88064384/1903-05-02/ed-1/?sp=1&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil&r=-0.007%2C0.473%2C0.642%2C0.421%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The Rockefeller fortune was founded
          upon credit capital. In 1375 John D.
          Rockefeller was a considerable oil
          merchant. But his schemes for mon
          opolizing the oil business of half the
          world were trembling between success
          and failure. In that year there were
          three weeks when he walked the floor
          night after night, sleepless, fighting
          the ruin that seemed to be closing in
          around him. It is said that his wife
          exclaimed: "I wish John would go
          bankrupt, for then he would get some
          sleep." It is said that the nervous in
          digestion which now compels him to
          the quietest of lives and to a diet of
          crackers and milk at 98 2-5 degrees
          Fahrenheit dates from that terrible
          three weeks. He owed the banks -of
          Cleveland 11,700,000. He could not pay;
          they were pressing him, but did not
          dare to close In upon him. They knew
          that if he failed it would swamp them
          and would precipitate a panic in
          Cleveland—Cleveland was not so large
          and rich in those days, and $1,700,000
          was a big sum of money, even in Wall
          street.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85033781/1905-03-03/ed-1/?sp=2&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Mr. Rockefeller does believe in th
          industrial system which he represents
          and which he has done so much to fur
          ther. His commercial creed is founded
          upon the theory of'the survival of the
          fittest.
          "We are better able to run your busi
          ness than you are. We will pay you a
          fair price for it and will conduct It our
          selves, but we will provide for you
          by paying you a salary to manage it (or
          to do whatever work you are best fit
          ted for), and you will thus have a cer
          tainty to depend upon Instead of the
          uncertainty and the possibility of losing
          your entire business which exists under
          the competitive system. Therefore, you
          will be better off than before. We will
          be better off because wo can m ike more
          money on a smaller margin of profit
          if we handle all tho business. The
          public will be better off because, through
          the economies of management on a large
          scale, it can secure its necessities at a
          lower or at least at a more regular price
          than before.
          "The fact that we make big fortunes
          for ourselves by this process is not un
          just, for we have demonstrated that we
          are more capable than the rqst of you
          by getting control of the business.
          Therefore wo are entitled to a gi eater
          reward, but we feel it our duty to help
          you by applying a part of our wealth
          to objects that will bo for tho public
          Ngood."
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn85042242/1905-07-01/ed-1/?sp=1&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil&st=text&r=0.235,0.572,0.24,0.314,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Ten million
          Collars as an endowment for higher
          education in the United States has
          been given the general education
          board by John D. Rockefeller. The
          announcement was made by Dr. Wal­
          lace Bufetrick of the board at a meet­
          ing during the day. The following
          letter to the secretaries and executive
          officers of the board from F. T. Gates,
          Mr. Rockefeller's representative, was
          given out:
          "I am authorized by Mr. John D.
          Rockefeller to say that he will con­
          tribute to the general education board
          the sum of $10,000,000 to be paid Oct.
          1 next in cash, or, at his option, in­
          come producing securities, at their
          market value, the principal to be held
          in perpetuity as a foundation for edu­
          cation, the income, above expenses
          and administration, to be distributed
          to or used for the benefit of such in­
          stitutions of learning, at such times, in
          such amounts, for such purposes and
          under such conditions, or employed in
          such other ways, as the board may
          deem best adapted to promote a com­
          prehensive system of higher education
          In the United States."
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn86072041/1909-04-06/ed-1/?sp=4&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          The complaint divides the devel
          opment of the alleged monopoly Into
          three periods: First, that from 1870
          Ito 1882 when the individual defend
          jants, John D. Rockefeller, William
          j Rockefeller, Henry M. Flagler and
          i others are described as forming the
          Standard and forcing competitors out
          of business; second, the period from
          1882 to 1899, when the Standard
          openly a "trust" operated under a
          trusteeship headed by John D. Rock
          efeller; third, the period from 1899
          to the time of the filing of the com
          plaint when the company organized
          under the laws of New Jersey, Its
          individual leadership lost behind its
          corporate personage, is alleged to
          have defined the United States and
          continually to have violated the
          Sherman anti-trust act.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn92061524/1914-10-03/ed-1/?sp=4&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Such .is the fact, for though not
          many know of it, John D. Rockefeller
          is a direct descendant of the reign
          ing house of England, a lineal heir of
          Edward Ironsides, once king, and of
          all the succeeding rulers down to Ed
          ward JII. Through the third Edward's
          son, the earl of Leicester, he traces
          his ancestry to the daughter of the
          third earl of Lincoln, who married
          John Humphrey, early magistrate .of
          Massachusetts Bay colony, and whose
          granddaughter, Susanna Palmes, wed
          Samuel Avery, progenitor of Lucy
          Avery, who married Godfrey Rocke
          feller, the giandsire of John D.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045487/1914-12-24/ed-1/?sp=25&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil&st=text&r=-0.205,0.088,1.29,1.29,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          JOHN D. HAS PURCHASED BIG
          HUNK OF GLORY
          New York, Dec. 24. In the last
          year John D. Rockefeller has pur
          chased ten and a half million dollars'
          worth of glory as an educational
          philanthropist by distributing that
          amount of money to state colleges
          and universities, according to a re
          port issued by the general education
          board. V
          Tennessee received $625,000; Tex
          as, $400,000; Ohio, $760,000; Illinois,
          $300,000; Minnesota, $350,000; Iowa,
          $596,516, and other states larger or
          smaller donations.
        </text>
      </result>
      <result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83045487/1915-09-01/ed-1/?sp=7&q=John+Rockefeller+Standard+Oil</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Miners are after
          John D. Rockefeller, Jr., tooth and
          nail, it became known reliably today.
          While a militia board of inquiry is
          probing charges in connection with
          reorganization of the state militia,
          and while, it is indicated, the federal
          government is taking a hand, it
          leaked out here today that as a re
          sult of this case and as an outgrowth
          of the John R. Lawson conviction, a
          concerted effort is under way to get
          criminal prosecution of Rockefeller
          and others in connection with death
          of more than 40 strikers in the re
          cent coal strikes.
        </text>
      </result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn84037890/1916-10-18/ed-1/?sp=3&q=john+d+rockefeller&r=0.088%2C0.234%2C0.735%2C0.481%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Frank Rocke
          feller, the, youngest of tho three
          brothers, who was recently brought
          into prominence by William's effort
          to bring about a reconciliation be
          tween him and John Is an Inter
          esting figure.
          Although poor when compared to
          the other two Rockefuters, Frank is
          not by any means an object of char
          ity. Ho abhors abovu all else to be
          spoken of as "John L. Rockefeller's
          brother."
          William's effort to end tho feud
          which has existed since 189S failed
          and John D. and Frank nre still as
          far apart as ever.
          It Is estimated that Jno. D. Rocke
          feller's wealth is $1,000,000,000.
          The sum involved which, it Is alleg
          ed led to the feud with his brother,
          was but $150,000.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn87065163/1907-07-08/ed-1/?sp=2&q=john+d+rockefeller&st=text&r=0.002,0.179,0.625,0.625,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          John D. Rockefeller, unscrupulous and devout, is not a hypocrite. The
          cloak of hypocrisy is too transparent; it would have been worn thread
          bare long ago. He is simply a contradiction. He is thoroughly honest
          in the belief that he is essentially a good man. So is his belief in the
          scriptures; but as you and I, reader, do not apply every rule of the Bible
          to ourselves, so does Rockefeller accept its truths, with the reservation
          that every rule has its exceptions. The parable of the Rich Man and the
          Needle does not apply to him. From his entrance into business life, he
          has set aside a portion of his income for the poor,—he loves to dwell on
          fact—. He has kept an account book with heaven, and will show you the
          credit and debtor side with a humility closely resembling pride. But he
          that those account books are his
          and is honest in the belief,
          passports to heaven.
          To the morbid mind such a contradiction may cast discredit upon our
          faith; to the honest searcher after truth, John D. Rockefeller is but the
          type of the two Impulses drawing us, the one to heaven, the other to tbe
          place we all hope to avoid. Both have developed in him to a rare de
          gree; that is what makes him so prominent.
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn87065501/1905-04-15/ed-1/?sp=3&q=john+d+rockefeller&r=0.193%2C0.258%2C1.123%2C0.735%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Two important items of John D.
          Rockefeller’s fortune are frequently
          overlooked in making computations of
          his wealth. These are his holdings of
          real estate and mortgages and of gov
          ernment and municipal bonds. Both are
          so vast that if we undertook to follow
          out the threads that lead to them they
          would take us to every part of the Unit
          ed States and across the Atlantic.
          While Mr. Rockefeller’s real estate
          holdings would amount to probably
          $10,000,000, such investment does not
          prove a very attractive venture for the
          astute financier. He prefers to let the
          other fellow own the real estate and he
          hold the mortgage. 
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn83030214/1919-06-29/ed-2/?sp=62&q=john+d+rockefeller&st=text&r=0.33,0.639,0.648,0.648,0</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          Miss Mina Smyth, daughter of Will?
          iam Smyth, who many times talked
          with John D. Rockefeller, in a recent
          statement said of him
          "One thing about Mr. Rockefeller
          that struck me as peculiar was that he
          seemed a little one-sided in his way
          of looking at things. For instance,
          there were his religious views. So
          far as he was concerned, there was
          just one church in the world, and
          that was the Baptist. He did wonders,
          so far as giving goes, for the freemen
          and the Indians in the Baptist mis?
          sions down South, but when I talked
          to him about the Presbyterian mission
          at Asheville he said that he had never
          heard of it. But he had the name
          and all about every Baptist concern
          in the country at his tongue's end, so j
          J. suppose he had enough to think of
          without troubling his head about other
          denominations."
        </text>
      </add_result>
      <add_result>
        <id>https://www.loc.gov/resource/sn92070446/1899-04-14/ed-1/?sp=2&q=john+d+rockefeller&r=0.418%2C0.15%2C0.468%2C0.306%2C0&st=text</id>
        <rel>1</rel>
        <text>
          John D. Rockefeller, now probably
          ths richest man In the world, spent his
          boyhood in a little house about three
          miles out of Owego, N. Y. When he
          was seven years old his father moved
          from a small farm of ninety acres near
          Owasso Lake, Just north of Moravia.
          Me was a poor farmer, this elder Rock
          efeller. ite was rarely at home, and
          a hired man did all the work of the
          farm.
          John D. Rockefeller grew up like
          the country boys he played with. He
          wag like his mother, and he learned
          his thrift from her. The house he liv
          ed In was one of the humblest In that
          neighborhood. It stands now exactly
          as when the young Rockefellers used
          to tumble down the steep back stair
          way or clamber over the low roof, a
          story and a half building, painted
          brown, with no porch and no wings,
          and almost too small to furnish elbow
          room for a family of six.
        </text>
      </add_result>
    </results>
  </topic>

</topics>
